Moustafa Ali

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mostafa-ali-61161a259?

utm_source=share&utm_campaign=share_via&utm_content=profile&utm_medium=android_app (

SUMMARY

I am good at dealing with the challenges of fast-paced professional and banking environments. Bringing a detailed and decisive nature with sound judgment, good multi-tasking abilities and a self-motivated personality. Comfortable working alone or with teams completing clerical tasks on time and accurately.

I have experience with accounting operations and how to deal with them.

I have experience in sales and marketing.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce in Accounting Department

Cairo University

= 09/2017 - 07/2021

EXPERIENCE

Employee in the Public Prosecution

Digital Public Prosecution

05/2023 - Present

Digital public prosecution offices provide traffic prosecution services, criminal prosecution services, and family prosecution services

Accountant

Bernasos Stationery

01/2023 - 05/2023

Bernasos Co.for industry, Trade & Stationeries.

Sales

Siwa Ranches

06/2021 - 10/2021

A natural and healthy food company

Receptionist

Butterfly Clinic

= 09/2020 - 01/2021

Dental clinic

SKILLS

Knowledge seeker Problem solving Researching Time management Active listening

Data analysis

LANGUAGES

Arabic Native

••••

English Advanced



TRAINING / COURSES

Summer Training At Banque Misr

Microsoft office Courses

Digital marketing courses